Guide to the William A. Speck Collection of Goetheana: General Ephemera
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Posters and Broadsheets, 1897-1932; Series V; 21
  - Mephisto. Copying. L & C. Hardtmuth (Atelier Neumann). Colored poster, undated; 19" x 12" (Box 24 Broadside)
  - Westmann, Räumungs-Verkauf. Lith. u. Druck v. Nauck & Hartmann (Berlin). Colored poster for a clearance sale (Faust motif), undated; 28" x 37" (Box 25 Broadside)
  - Columbia Records (Faust and Gretchen), 1919 October; 36" x 13" (Box 26 Broadside)
  - Columbia Grafonola (Faust and Gretchen), undated; 18" x 12" (Box 27 Broadside)
  - Goethewoche Karlsbad., 1932 July 10-18; 37" x 25" (Box 28 Broadside)
  - German Tourist Information Office, New York/ Reichsbahnzentrale für den deutschen Reiseverkehr, Berlin., 1932; 29" x 20", 2 copies (Box 29 Broadside)
  - Goethejahr 1932 Weimar. Gedenkfeiern und Festspiele vom 20. März bis 20 Sept., 29" x 20" (Box 30 Broadside)
  - Goethe und seine Werke. Zum 100. Todestage am 22. März 1832, 1932; 25" x 17" (Box 31 Broadside)
  - Und wer der Dichtkunst Stimme nicht vernimmt... Leipzig: Börsenverein der Deutschen Buchhändler, undated; 24" x 17" (Box 32 Broadside)
  - Volkswohl-Lotterie für Winterhilfe, Feb.-Mar. 1932. (Werther's Lotte with siblings), undated; 18" x 13" (Box 33 Broadside)
- Oversize Material, (3 boxes)
  - Paper ephemera related to Goethe/Schiller coins and medals, early twentieth century (in Series I) (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Faust and Gretchen in the street, colored print (in Series I) (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Faust and Gretchen embracing. Two lithophanes, one alabaster (?) in a wood frame, the other dark blue plastic-like material (in Series I) (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Oil painting, Faust and Gretchen in the garden (in Series I) (Box 11)
  - Wooden plaque with incised quotation from Goethe's letter to Lavater (in Series IV) (Box 12)